Abdallah Moussa

Front-End Developer

Contact

- 🌭 01127124302 01090802294
- Mahallah.moussa.2017@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/In/abdallah-moussa
- 21th street Elgnayen Suez, Egypt
- Abdallah Moussa Portfolio

Education

-Bachelor's Degree in Computer

Science. (Grade: Good)

Faculty of Computer and Information,

Suez Canal University. (2015-2019)

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS, CSS3
- Media Query
- Tailwind
- Java Script
- jQuery
- React Js
- Next Js

Additional Skills

- PHP/ Laravel
- Mysql
- Data Structure & Algorithms

Summary

Innovative Front-End developer with more one year experience in web development, loving coding and challenges. I have a big passion to learn new technologies, I have a good experience in HTML, CSS, JS plus modern libraries and frameworks like React Js and Next Js.

I looking forward to have my own technology that compete with current modern technology.

Work Experience

Front End Developer

- OCD Digital Services Company, Suez October 2022 – Present.
- Implement responsive web applications using React.js, HTML5, CSS3, tailwind and JavaScript.
- Built reusable and modular components, ensuring clean and maintainable codebase.
- Improving application performance and data flow.
- Free Lancing

January 2022 – Present.

Work in many large websites, resolve issues and improve performance

- SGS Dass, s4sensors, Xper-erp.. etc.

Projects

- Julia-Shopping "E-commerce website with React.js" Libraries..
 - React.js, React Router Dom, Redux/toolkit, React icons and Swiper Slider

 Live Demo
- More Projects on GitHub and Code Pin

Military Service Completed "good idol"